Guide to the Stanford University, Asian American Activities Center, Records SC0487
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Asian American Students' Association (AASA) records, Series 2
  - AASA 1986-1987] (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - AASA Social Committee [1990-1991] (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - AASA Social Committee (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Phone Lists (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - AASA [1982-1983] (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Asian American [1981-1982] (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - AASA Issues Committee (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - AASA Previous Budgets (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - AASA Culture and Education (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - AASA Fee Assessment (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - AASA General / Outreach (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - AASA Issues Committee, Asian American Studies (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - New Winds Newsletter [1989-1990] (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Asia America (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Asian American Student Organizations, Series 3
  - Stanford Hong Kong Students Association (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Stanford Hawaii Club (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Asian American Christian Fellowship (AACF) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Chinese Folk Dancing (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Half Asian People's Association (HAPA) 1990-91 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Stanford Vietnamese Association [1990-91] (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Old Skas [1991] (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Asian Law Students Association (ALSA) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - A/PI Endorsements (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Asian Youth Project [1990-91] (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - East Coast Asian Student Union (ECASU) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Asian American Medical Students (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Stanford Hong Kong Student Association (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Student Organization Services Info [1990-1991] (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Korean American Students Association (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Korean Students Association (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Asian American Activities Center
  - Asian American New Student Orientation (AANSOC)
    - AANSOC [1983-1984] (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - AANSOC T-Shirt Design (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - AANSOC [1990-91] (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Big Sib Little Sib Program
    - AANSOC Big Sib and Little Sib [1982] (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Big Sib / Little Sib Program (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Big Sib / Little Sib [1987-1988] (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Big Sib / Little Sib [1988-1989] (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Asian Pacific American Student Union (APSU)
    - Asian/Pacific Islander Student Union (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - APSU Cultural Night (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - APSU (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - APSU Mail out (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Stanford University Nikkei (SUN)
    - SUN (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Stanford University Nikkei [1990-91] (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Stanford University Nikkei (SUN) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Asian American Graduate Students
    - Asian American Graduate Students (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Asian American Graduate Students Association (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Graduate Students (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Asian American Graduate Students Association (AAGSA) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Asian American Business Student Association
    - Asian American Business Association [1990-91] (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Asian American Business Student Association (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Ho'Oikaika (Native Hawaiian)
    - Ho'Oikaika (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Ho'Oikaia (Native Hawaiian) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Misc non-student files
    - Unity Network [1988-89] (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Stanford Asian / Pacific American Alumni Club (SAPAAC) [1990-91] (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Asian Staff Forum (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Asian Staff Forum, List (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Asian Staff Forum [1990-91] (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Asian American Art Series, Series 4
  - Asian American Art Series, Unbound Feet, Poetry / Dramatic Monologue [Winter 1980] (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Asian American Theater Project (AATP), Paper Angels [1988] (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - AA Art Series, Asian American Theater Workshop [Winter 1980] (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - AA Art Series, Asian American Musicians Organization [Winter 1980] (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - AA Art Series, Nelly Wong, Poetry [Winter 1980] (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - AA Art Series, George Leong, Fiction [Winter 1980] (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - AA Art Series, Nancy Araki, Visual Communications, Film [Winter 1980] (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - AA Art Series, Proposal (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - AA Art Series, Philip Gotanda, Artist-in-Residence, Song for a Nisei Fisherman [Winter 1980] (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - AA Art Series, Carlos Villa, Painting (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - AA Art Series, Asian American Dance Collective [Winter 1980] (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Asian Americans and the Media; Asian American Politics; Asian American History and other miscellaneous documents, Series 5
  - Asian Americans and the Media
    - Asians and the San Francisco Media (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Asian Images - a Message to the Media (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Asian Americans: Let's Make it (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - The Intellectual and the Mass Media (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Ambush at Kamikaze Pass (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Adhesive Tape Orientals (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Asian American for a Fair Media (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - All the News that Sells (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Another Government: The News Media (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Notes on Stereotypes and Stereotyping (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Media Monitor (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - The Media Barons and the Public Interest (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - A Look at the Caricatures of the Asians (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - An Interview with Jan Yanehiro (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - FCC: Regulation of Programming in the Public Interest (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - How Children's Books Distort the Asian American Image (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - The Reporter as Activist (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Print media should revise its mission (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - The Politics of News Media Control (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - The Perils of Newspaper Literacy (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Asians in Mass Media Newsletter (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Asians in the Media: The Shadows in the Spotlight (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - The Bay Area's One and Only (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Blacks on TV: a Disturbing Image (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - A China Man's Chance Revisited (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Commercial TV - Portrayal of Woman and Minorities (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Confessions of the Chinatown Cowboy (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Don't Worry Judge, It's just us (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Asian Stereotypes in Film (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Some Effects of Mass Media (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - The Television Audience and Program Mediocrity (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Television Pollutes Us All (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Toward Barefoot Journalism (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - It Ain't All Smiles and Sukiyaki (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Interview - Tommy Chung and Russel Valpariso (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Interview - Tommy Chung and Russel Valpariso; Copy 2 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Asian American Politics
    - Asian American Identity and Politics; Copy 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Asian American Identity and Politics; Copy 2 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Asian American Identity and Politics; Copy 3 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Asian American Identity and Politics (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Asian American Identity and Politics (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - The Emergence of the Asian-American Movement (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Some Thoughts on Asian America Today (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Rocky Road: North American Politics and Asian America (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - An Interview with Warren Furutani (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - The Significance of Asian in American Society (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Workshops on Political and Social Issues (SWOPSI) 186: Asian American and the Media
    - SWOP 186, Asian American and the Media [8] - readings (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - SWOP 186, Asian American and the Media [6] - readings (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - SWOP 186, Asian American and the Media [7] - readings (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - SWOP 186, Asian American and the Media [5] - readings (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - SWOP 186, Asian American and the Media [4] - readings (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - SWOP 186, Asian American and the Media [3] - readings (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - SWOP 186, Asian American and the Media [2] - readings (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Asian American History
    - Chinese Immigrants (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Rediscovered Voices: Chinese Immigrants and Angel Island (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - The New Immigrants (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Shifting Occupational and Class Structures 1930-1966 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - America is in the Heart, an Excerpt; Copy 3 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - America is in the Heart, an Excerpt; Copy 2 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - America is in the Heart, an Excerpt (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - The Filipino: Looking for a better life (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - 1960 - today; New Era of Struggle (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Japanese American History
      - Nisei in Hawaii (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Legal Aspects of the Japanese American Relocation (Box 3, Folder 83)
      - The Japanese as Workers and their Responses to Plantation Conditions (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Japanese in Hawaii (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Japanese in Hawaii before World War II (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Farewell to Manzanar (Box 3, Folder 95)
      - Small Business and Japanese American Solidarity (Box 3, Folder 77)
      - Hito Hata (Box 3, Folder 96)
      - The Japanese and Japanese Americans (Box 3, Folder 84)
      - Cultural Conflicts and Accommodations of the first and second Generation Japanese (Box 3, Folder 92)
      - The Evacuation of the Japanese During World War II (Box 3, Folder 93)
      - Socio-Psychological Effects of the Concentration Camp Experience (Box 3, Folder 91)
      - Nisei: The quiet American? (Box 3, Folder 74)
      - Small Business and Japanese American Ethnic Solidarity (Box 3, Folder 78)
      - Nisei: The quiet American? a Re-evaluation (Box 3, Folder 75)
      - A Case Study of San Francisco's Japan town (Box 3, Folder 80)
      - Critical Reviews of: Japanese Americans: The Untold Story (1971) (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Asian American History (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Asian American Issues
    - "The Broken Ladder": Asian Americans in City Government (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Asian American Employment (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Employment Policy Recommendations (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Readings on Racism and Race Relations in Hawaii (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Toward a Political Economy of Chinese America; Copy 1 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Toward a Political Economy of Chinese America; Copy 2 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Toward a Political Economy of Chinese America; Copy 3 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Need for Awareness, an essay on Chinatown, S.F. (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Need for Awareness, an essay on Chinatown, S.F. (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Employment Discrimination against the Chinese (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Employment Discrimination against the Chinese (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Asian Americans and Mental Health
    - Why do People go or don't go to the Doctor? (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Personality and Mental Health: A Clarification (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - The Shame Factor: Counseling Asian Americans (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - What the Citizen can do (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - The Failure of Democracy in a Time of Crisis (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - An Introduction to Asian American Writing (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Silicon Valley Blues (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Profiles (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Educational Record (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - The Chinese in South-East Asia: A longer View (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Asian American Campus and Political Issues; Publications; Asian American Activities Center and other miscellaneous documents, Series 6
  - Stanford: Course Descriptions (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - News Clippings (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - News Clippings (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Rainbow Agenda; Minority Affairs (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Western Culture (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Asian American Activities Center (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - University of Oregon Survey: Asians and Attitudes towards Elderly (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Building Our Future (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Asians and American: News Articles (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - SWOPSI 112: From Stereotypes to Revolution (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Public Service (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - R R - Civil Liberties Act of 1987 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Proposition 63 - English Only (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - UC Berkeley: Study on Asian Immigrants (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Western Culture (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Education [incl. Western Culture] (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - 1989-1990 Asians and Americans (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Signature Lists (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Legal Affairs (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Student Support Fundamental Standard (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Political Support Network Meetings Minutes (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Dean's Stuff (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Native American People Today (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - People's Platform (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Students for a Free China (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - CODE (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Student Labor Support Coalition (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Ethnic Studies as a Requirement (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Admissions Policy (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - People's Platform Campaign / Election (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - 1985 Proposed Budget Cuts for Federal Student Financial Aid (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - History 267; Asian American History (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Asian American Books - Catalogs (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Newspapers / Publications (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Asian American Books - SU Libraries (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Movies (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Source books (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Lunar New Year (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The Teahouse (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Okada House 1990-91 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Fall Activities 1990-91 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Joey's Stuff (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Asian American Activities Center Bulletin (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Asian American Activities Center proposals
    - Asian American Activities Center: Proposal 1987 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Asian American Activities Center: Proposals / Petitions (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Asian American Activities Center, Funding Proposal (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Asian American Studies, Series 7
  - Charlesworth: Units 15,16, 19; copy 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Charlesworth: Units 15,16, 19; copy 2 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Charlesworth: Units 15,16, 19; copy 3 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Charlesworth: Units 15,16, 19; copy 4 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Psychological Problems of Asian and Asian American Students; Stanford (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Asian American Peer Counselors (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Local, Regional, and National Listings of Asian American Organizations (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - SWOPSI 187B; Chinese Immigrant Women (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - SWOPSI 187B; Interracial Dating (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - SWOPSI 187B; Wrap up; Food for Thought (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - SWOPSI 187B; Asian Women and Third World Women (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Chinatown 1973 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Asian American Studies, other institutions
    - Asian American Studies, Other Universities (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - California State University, Sacramento; UCLA; Asian American Studies (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - UCLA; Asian American Studies (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - UCLA; Asian American Studies (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - UC Berkeley; Asian American Studies (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - UC Berkeley; Asian American Studies (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - UCLA; Asian American Studies (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - San Jose State University; Asian American Studies (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - California State University, S.F.; Asian American Studies (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Harvard; Asian American Studies (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - US Davis; Asian American Studies (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - UCLA; Asian American Studies (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Inter-Racial Relations (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Readings for SWOPSI 182; Asian American Communities (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Asian Immigration Economic and Social Perspective (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Bridge Articles: I am Yellow ... Curious? Myth of the Exotic Erotic (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Lau v. Nichols: History of a Struggle for Equal and Quality Education (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Lau v. Nichols - Two Years After (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - The Political and Economic Effects of Urban Renewal on Ethnic Communities (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - The Significance of Asians in American Society (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - SWOPSI; Ethnic Theme Houses (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Contemporary Issues of Asian Americans (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - SWOPSI 151; Asian American Studies [Spring 1974] (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - SWOPSI 182; Asian American Communities (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Prof. Befu, TA Chan: Asian American Identity (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Plant Services Receipts (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Student Organization Services (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Asian American Studies; 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Asian American Conferences (Miscellaneous) (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - SWOPSI 184; Asian American: Perspectives through Generations (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Moynihan, Graduation 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Fukuda, AB 173 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Asian Neighborhood Design (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - SWOPSI 184, Arleen Armstrong (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Report of UGS-22 Class Project (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - SWOPSI 186: Asian Americans and the Media-Emerging Perspectives (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - SWOPSI 184 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Asian American Studies: UGS 155a and 155b: The History of the Asian Americans 1848-1945 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Asian American Studies 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - UGS 22: Historical Perspectives of Asian Americans [Fall 1974-75] (Box 6, Folder 12)
- News Clippings, Series 8
  Scope and Contents
  This subseries contains newsclippings pertaining to the Agenda for Action Coalition, a multi-ethnic coalition of students who, in 1989, occupied then President Donald Kennedy's office in what was known as the "Take Over," to demand more university attention to multicultural education, including establishment of ethnic studies, hiring ethnic studies faculty, and, the institutionalization of the ethnic community centers.
  - Paper Clippings; Asian Americans (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Daily (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Press Contacts (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - News Clippings 1988-89 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - News Clippings 1989 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Theater, "The Fire Within" (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Asian American publications; Asian American Women; Asian Americans at Stanford; Asian American Community Organizations and Issues; Redress and Reparations; and Assorted Files, Series 9
  This series contains the early publications of the Asian American Activities Center (Asian American Bulletin) and the Asian American Students Association (Winds). Included are materials pertaining to the Stanford Asian Students Coordinating Committee (SASCC), which replaced the Asian American Students Alliance in 1973, and later became the Asian American Students Association in 1976. Other documents pertain to the history of Asian Americans at Stanford in the early 1970's and 1980's.
  - Sourcebook (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Asian-American Studies (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Sourcebook Raw Material (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Talking Stories - Fall 1980-81 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Orientation 1989; Banquet (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Leaders workshop / retreat (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Asian American Students' Association Outreach Info (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Asian American Students' Association, Notes (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Essays on Asian American Problems (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Contemporary Issues (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - History (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Personal (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Essays on Asian American Issues (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Asian Pacific Islander Magazine, vol. 1, no. 1-2, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Expressions - Volume II No. 1 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Expressions - Volume II No. 2 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Asian American Bulletin
    - Asian American Bulletin; Masters [1984-85] (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Asian American Bulletin - Volume VI (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Asian American Bulletin - Volume VIII (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Asian American Bulletin; Masters [1982-83] (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Asian American Bulletin - Volume X (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Asian American Bulletin - Volume VIII [1985] (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Asian American Bulletin - Volume VI (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Asian American Bulletin - Volume V (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Asian American Bulletin - Volume IV (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Asian American Bulletin - Volume III (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Asian American Bulletin - Volume II (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Asian American Bulletin - Volume I (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Redress and Reparations for Japanese Americans
    - 1979-80 Redress and Reparations (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - 1980-81 Redress and Reparations (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Redress and Reparations Committee (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Redress and Reparations Committee; Outreach (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Redress and Reparations; Documents (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - 1980 Tule Lake Pilgrimage (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Film Info (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Publications Board (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Yellow Pages 1976-77 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Stanford News 1975-76 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Community Organizations [1984-85] (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Annual Report (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Open House (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - AACI / S.F. Journal [1978-79] (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - AACI Minutes Agenda [1975] (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Committee on Service to Students (COSS) (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Chinese for Affirmative Action (CAA) (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Admissions and Financial Aid [1975-76] (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Minority Finances, Moynihan Affair (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Asian Americans at Stanford 1971-1976
    - Asian Americans at Stanford [1975-76] (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Asian Americans at Stanford Pre-1972-73 (mostly 1971) (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Stanford Asian Students Coordinating Committee (SASCC) 1974-75 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Stanford Asian Students Coordinating Committee (SASCC) 1975-76 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - For Resource Center Bulletin (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Winds
    - Winds (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Winds Copy #3 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Winds Business [1977-78] (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Winds - International Hotel (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Winds Business - 1976-77 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Winds Correspondence 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Winds - General Info (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Asian American Women
    - Winds - Asian American Women (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Asian American Women's Journal (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - A Women's Guide to Stanford, Asian Pacific Islander Magazine (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Asian American Women's Group Finances (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Feminism in Color, Workshop [Fall 1977] (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Asian American Women's Journal [1989] (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Stanford Asian Women [1990-91] (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Asian American Women (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Asian American Women's Material (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Asian American Women's Journal (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Other Campuses 1984-85 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Asian American Community Organizations (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Asians Have Made It; or Have They? (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Career Planning and Placement Center; Annual Report 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Asian American Activities Center; Asian American Studies; Asian American Theater Project; Asian Staff Forum; Agenda for Action and Take-Over; University Committee on Minority Issues (UCMI); Junipero; and other miscellaneous documents, Accession ARCH_1997_073
  - Articles through 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Asian American Activities Center
    - Asian American Sourcebook (Box 6)
    - Asian American Sourcebook (Box 6)
    - Asian American Activities Center miscellaneous: brochures and newsletter (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Asian American Activities Center survey findings: Asian American resources (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Communicasians newsletter (Box 4, Folder 9)